right Apple number 21 this is much
easier than I thought it was going to be
they just keep coming
I mean not that I've had mony ideas I've
had many of these ideas before but they
just keep flying back and I'll put this
one out with this one anyway sorry
today's app today's today these have all
been on the same day
Apple number 21 is a divorce app so I've
never gotten married and therefore never
gotten divorce but I do have a child and
have friends with children and the
amount of conflict that comes from
divorce I feel there's a way we can all
be more amicable where we can form small
groups where people who are going
through it you'll to Bent about Rx and
find peaceful loving solutions not just
be a space to be like he's an asshole
but also be a space of like have you
thought about it from his side and like
you he only gets them every other
weekend that seems like that's not you
know he doesn't seem to get think of the
time maybe it's not fair maybe anyway
having a space where you can discuss it
having a space that helps communication
between exes who has the kids when who's
responsible for what
that recital is on this state whether
the other person's coming I mean all the
conflicts that are go back and forth in
text just having one place to hold that
I mean I guess another idea away for
maybe the other idea my divorce that so
helping with co-parenting your children
even pets if you want who has custody
coordinating you're sure how our being
warehouses are the kids have a house I
mean finding solutions that make it as
easy as possible on the kids and don't
leave the next generation scarred from
divorce that is idea number 21